https://macgillivrayfreeman.com/privacy-policy/

Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information
Last Updated May 18, 2020
Thank you for visiting the MacGillivray Freeman Films website. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our practices for information collected via the Site, how such information is used, the circumstances under which we disclose such information to third parties and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this Privacy Policy so you can understand how we use your personal information.When we use the term “personal information” we mean information such as your first/middle initial or name and last name, street address, town or city, state, zip code, telephone number, instant-messenger user ID, blog or other personal website URL, date of birth, e-mail address and any other information that would allow someone to identify you or contact you. Personal information also includes information about your personal preferences, survey or application responses and your transactions or relationship with us, if you have been a user of the Site or you have provided this type of information to the Company or its affiliates.This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Use. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the ascribed to them in the Terms of Use. We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use often for updates.Your continued use of the Site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your personal information as described herein. This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect as long as you are a user of the Site, even if your use of or participation in any particular service, feature, function or promotional activity terminates, expires, ceases, is suspended or deactivated for any reason.The Information We Collect
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e., generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 2000 or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online or Earthlink). We also may collect personal information about you when you visit the Site and input information, whether you are registering to use any services, features or functions of the Site,), or otherwise in the course of any other exchanges of information, transactions and activities. During registration (and possibly at certain other times to enable your use of other features or functions or for security purposes), you will be required to provide us with certain information about you in order for us to allow you to use the features and functions that we may offer on the Site, such as chat rooms, message boards, electronic mail services, messaging services, registration and member profile pages.
How We Use and Disclose the Information
We may use the information we obtain from you, including personal information, to tailor your experience on the Site, to display content we think may be of interest to you, or to let us customize what you see when you visit the Site according to your preferences. We will use the personal information you provide online only for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include sending you an email about updates to the Site or about an upcoming event if you have signed up for updates. We also may conduct an occasional survey of our registered users, to see how our Site can better serve you. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services that we think you may be interested in. Finally, we may share your information with organizations that are affiliated with or related to the Company, its affiliates in connection with the provision of their respective information, products, materials and services or for marketing and/or administrative purposes. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please contact us at contact@macfreefilms.com.How We Share Your Personal Information
We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy (b) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (c) with your consent; (d) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g., in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request, or when we believe that someone is causing, or about to cause, injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); (e) with other persons or companies or affiliated or related organizations with whom we contract to carry out internal Site operations or our business activities (for example, third-party contractors — see below); (f) In the event of a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, transfer of control, joint venture or other business combination involving us or our affiliates. and/or (g) to notify you when we make changes to one of our subscriber agreements or this policy. Our business needs may change from time to time and we reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. We will not use your personal information in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, however, without first obtaining your consent to do so. If intended uses differ from this policy, we will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an “opt-in” or “opt-out” method, or by other means (such as sending to you an email).Our operations and maintenance contractors sometimes have limited access to your personal information in the course of providing products or services to the Company. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with email distribution technology, services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our Site. Access to your personal information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the contractor to perform its limited function for the Company. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors 1) protect the privacy of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and 2) not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than providing us with products and services as required by law.The Company is committed to protecting your privacy. We maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information and while no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your personal information.Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our Site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. We may also share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.Collection of Information by Others
Our Site may contain links to other Sites whose information practices may be different from ours. You should check the other sites’ privacy notices since we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them.Cookies
To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files that our web server places on your hard disk to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our Site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our Site). You can opt to have your browser reject cookies without any effect on your use of our Site. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our Site in order to participate in certain promotions. You should also know that companies that advertise on our Site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.Web Beacons
Some of our web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information, but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information, including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. Some of our web pages may also contain web beacons placed there to help us determine the effectiveness of our efforts to promote philanthropic partnership and investment opportunities, as well as other initiatives.Clickstream Data
As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a website’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the website from which you linked to the website. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of the Site, how visitors navigate throughout the Site, and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will be used only to improve our Site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and in the aggregate.Discussions and Community Tools; Testimonials
You agree that any information you submit to us through the Site may be used for promotional purposes. Because of the public nature of some of our services, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. We may also use a limited amount of information, such as first name, last initial, and your town and state in marketing materials on the Site. Your registration constitutes consent to this use.International Users
If you are visiting the Site from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using the Site, you authorize and specifically consent to the export of your personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of California and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the state of California.How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information
For instructions on how you can access the personal information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please send an email to contact@macfreefilms.com.To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We reserve the right to deny access, use and registration privileges to any user, including without limitation, a registered user, of any services, features or functions of the Site if we believe there is a question about the identity of the person trying to access the user’s account or any services, features or functions. And if the burden or expense of providing access to your personal information is disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or if the legitimate rights of others would be violated, we may decide not to provide access to such information. In such cases, we will provide to you an explanation of why access cannot be provided and contact information for further inquiries.Special Note for Parents
This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. The Site does not knowingly collect or store personal identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you have concerns about this Site or its services, if you want to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, or if you want to cancel your child’s membership, please contact us at contact@macfreefilms.com. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our Site without your permission, you may contact us at contact@macfreefilms.comTransfer of Business Assets
The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if the company, any or all of its subsidiaries or affiliates, or any of their assets is ever acquired by or merged into a third party.How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you may email contact@macfreefilms.com or write to the following address:MacGilllivray Freeman FilmsPO Box 205
Laguna Beach, CA 92652Get in touchP.O. Box 205
Laguna Beach, CA
92652 U.S.A. 949.494.1055949.494.2079contact@macfreefilms.comFollow usSign Up for Our NewsletterQuick LinksAbout UsAwards & AchievementsTeamStorytelling on the Giant ScreenDistributionEducation & ChangeFilmsCareersPrivacy Policy
© 2015 MacGillivray Freeman Films. IMAX® is a registered trademark of Imax Corporation. "Great Adventure Films" is a registered trademark of MacGillivray Freeman Films, Inc. Site powered 100% by Solar Energy | www.aiso.net. ‘ACADEMY AWARDS®’ is the registered trademark and service mark of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences
Contact UsWith two Academy Award nominations, one billion dollars at the box office, 60 films in 50 years, and hundreds of partnerships with the world’s leading institutions, we have a proven record of success.
What can we do for you?
Not readable? Change text.
Send
Start typing and press Enter to search
Sign up for our newsletter!Be the first to be know about MFF news and more.
United States of AmericaAaland IslandsAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua And BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Saint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuracaoCyprusCzech RepublicDemocratic Republic of the CongoDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mc Donald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJersey
(Channel Islands)JordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRepublic of KosovoReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoa (Independent)San MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSt. HelenaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos IslandsTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUSA Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City State (Holy See)VenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Subscribe
×
Share This
Facebook
Twitter
LinkedIn
Gmail
Yahoo Mail
